hitsdailydouble.com 2017-06-30

# Privacy Policy | HITS Daily Double

**Privacy Policy for** **HITS Daily Double**

Website Privacy Policy for  HITS Daily Double 

As of 03-30-2014

HITS Daily Double has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting personal information. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices relating to a website located at http://hitsdailydouble.com (the “Site” or the “Website”) and any mobile applications and other services that we may make available from time to time (collectively, the “Services”). The information you provide on this Site will not be shared other than as outlined in this Privacy Policy. By using the Services, you consent to the collection and use by us of any personal and other information you provide whilst using the Services in accordance with our Privacy Policy (this “Privacy Policy”). If you do not agree to the Privacy Policy, please do not use the Services.

Please carefully read our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions.

This Website presents information and content that is owned, licensed, or provided by HITS Daily Double its subsidiaries and affiliates ("Administrator"). The Site may also include services provided by third parties and distributed through the Site by virtue of a license, grant or some other form of agreement between the third party and Administrator. When used in this Privacy Policy, "we", “us” and "our" mean Administrator.

**Visiting Our Website**

You can use the Services without providing any personal or individually identifiable information by sending an email with a request to do so.  The request should include your name, email address, login information, and any specifics that may help us to prevent the collection of personally identifiable information you do not wish to have collected or disclosed. You may also be able to set the security settings on your browser to prevent certain tracking and logging features. If you opt to restrict the information we collect, the Services may be less functional for you.

There are times when you may choose to give us personally identifiable information about yourself. For example, you may wish to register, make purchases, read articles, view information, receive e-mails from us, receive invitations to attend events, participate in discussions, preview new services, or participate in special promotions. If you register to use the Services or if you conduct transactions through the Site or any related mobile applications, we will collect information about the transactions you engage in and your other activities. We need certain information from you to register you, authenticate you, process your entries and payments, and send goods to you, as necessary.

**Kinds of Information We Collect**

We may collect information that you voluntarily give us, as well as location-based information and site visitorship data as described below.

Personally Identifiable Information

In order to take advantage of certain features, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information about you that would enable someone to contact you directly. Personally identifiable information may include your e-mail address, name, postal/mailing address, telephone numbers, social security number, credit card details, shipping and billing addresses, or a persistent identifier (such as a customer number held in a cookie) which is associated with personally identifiable information, as well as other information that you may provide voluntarily. We collect such personally identifiable information that you give us so that we may:

• provide you with information about the Services;

• tell you about products and services and provide information to our third party marketing partners, subject to this policy;

• notify you about new features available through the Services;

• respond to your requests for information;

• process survey results and other data you provide;

• process contest entries;

• process online purchases and payments;

• you products you order;

• filter the products and information we offer; and

• open, maintain and administer user accounts.

• post your comments and content.

We will use the personally identifiable information we collect to provide you with specific information and services that you request, and with additional information and services that may be of interest to you. By providing your personally identifiable information, you fully understand and consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States of America and other countries. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring a password and user ID, before granting access to your data. While we strive to protect our user's personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk. We will provide you reasonable access to personal information that you provided through the Website and the reasonable ability to review and correct it, as applicable. We may also collect non-personal information such as your IP address and use 'cookies' on the website. The information obtained from collecting IP addresses and using 'cookies' is not personal information about you. For more information, please read the sections on IP addresses and cookies below.

Location-Based Information

We may collect information relating to your general location based on (1) information you manually provide, (2) the IP address of your computer, (3) Global Positioning System (GPS) information sent to us by your GPS-enabled device, and (4) the proximity of your laptop computer, mobile wireless device, personal digital assistant, personal communication system, or other communications device (your “Personal Communication Device”) to the nearest radio tower or cell site. We may also be able to detect when your Personal Communication Device is activated as well as when and how you are using it. We may collect data to verify the information you provide manually and to provide you with location-based content. We may associate Personally Identifiable Information with location-based information provided by you or your Personal Communication Device solely for our internal use and to improve your experience with the Services.

Site Visitorship Data

Site Visitorship Data is information about the way a website is used that is not associated with an individual’s identity. We use anonymous data regarding online behavior to better understand how people use our Services. To that end, we may use and disclose aggregated, anonymous online traffic behavior along with information from third parties to track usage trends and thereby improve the Services. We may also use and disclose this aggregated, anonymous information to develop reports that we may share with third party marketing partners and affiliates. The kind of information we may collect includes:

• the date and time you access the Services;

• your internet service provider, mobile carrier, or data services provider;

• your Internet Protocol (IP) address;

• the pages you visit;

• the products you purchase and review;

• the links you click;

• the features used;

• how and when you interact with the Services;

• the content, images and advertisements you select; and

• how you arrived at the Services and where you go when you leave.

Most Site Visitorship Data is collected using data collection tools such as web beacons, cookies, embedded web links and other software (together, “Data Collection Tools”).  Data Collection Tools are typically small data files or software that are sent to your browser and stored on your computer's or mobile device's hard drive. Most browsers and display software can be set to inform you when Data Collection Tools are being used or other tracking software is being sent to your computer or Personal Communication Device. They also provide you with the option of refusing such Data Collection Tools. However, refusing to allow the use of Data Collection Tools may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, certain areas or features of the Services, including preventing you from purchasing products or services.

Data Collection Tools may store the information in your shopping cart and allow us to relate your use of the Services to other information about you, including your Personal Information. We may do this to improve and personalize your experience with the Services and help resolve problems you experience through your use of the Services.

We use Site Visitorship Data to develop, manage, and improve the Website. Sometimes we may aggregate Site Visitorship Data with personal information from registered members. We may use that information to:

• manage the Website;

• help resolve problems;

• analyze use of the site; and

• tell you about products or services that our third party marketing partners, members and we may offer.

**Disclosure of Information**

Administrator will not release any personal information to third parties without your consent except as follows:

(1) Anyone providing us their personally identifiable information grants us and our affiliates the right to use their information for the provision of Services to you and for the benefit of Administrator without restrictions for the purposes that include, without limitation, research, marketing, and content and lead development.  Administrator does not collect or disclose personally identifiable information that is unrelated to these purposes.  And if we wish to disclose personally identifiable information we have collected for purposes other than those stated in this Privacy Policy, we will ask for your consent to do so.

(2) Administrator may share information we collect with our business and third party marketing partners. If we share your information, we will request that such third parties treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and refrain from disclosing or using your personally identifiable information for purposes other than for the provision of Services to you or for the benefit of Administrator. Our third party marketing partners may also send you special promotions and offers for related services, at their sole discretion. To the extent required, you hereby authorize this use of your personally identifiable information.

(3) We may disclose information collected on this site, including personal information, to third parties as required or permitted by law. For example, we may disclose information:

• to regulators;

• to law enforcement authorities pursuant to an official request;

• to vendors who provide us with service; or

• to companies that may acquire part or all of Administrator or an affiliated company.

Administrator is not responsible for the protection of the information you provide to other websites. You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information on other websites, such information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited communications.

**Advertising**

We may use third-party companies to serve ads and provide content through the Services. These companies may use cookies and other Data Collection Tools that are not sent by us to learn about your use of the Services and other websites and apps in order to present personalized advertisements and other messages that may be of interest to you. Administrator is not responsible for such cookies and tracking software.

**Commercial Transactions**

Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other reasons, we decide to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize our business. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personally identifiable information to prospective or actual purchasers or joint venture partners, or the receipt of it from sellers. It is our practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.

**Information Security**

Whenever you enter an area of the site that carries or requires you to enter sensitive information such as your credit card details, a padlock icon will appear in the address bar of your browser, indicating that the page is secure. Administrator uses the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and Private Communications Technology security standards that are supported by popular browsers. SSL encodes your personal information by encrypting credit card number, name, address, phone number, identification number and your password so that they cannot be read by unauthorized parties. While we may provide encryption technologies and use other reasonable precautions to protect confidential information and provide suitable security, we do not guarantee that information transmitted through the Internet is secure, or that such transmissions will be free from delay, interruption, interception or error.

We have put in place certain physical, technological and managerial procedures to safeguard the personally identifiable information we collect. However, these procedures do not guarantee that the information will remain secure against theft or misuse.

**Communications**

From time to time, Administrator may communicate with you regarding your transactions and the administration of your account, current projects, special offers, invitations to events, offers for services, product testing opportunities, updates to the Services, press releases, announcements concerning new services we provide, contests and sweepstakes, as well as important changes in our and this Privacy Policy. By providing us with your e-mail address and/or your mobile phone number, you consent to receiving such communications. If at any time you decide for any reason that you no longer wish to receive such communications, you may “opt out” of receiving them by using one of the following methods:

• Select the "opt out" or "unsubscribe" link, or follow the opt-out instructions that may be included in such communication.

• Where applicable, return to the web page(s) or service where you originally registered your preferences and follow the opt-out instructions.

• E-mail us at .  Be sure to provide your name, e-mail address and postal address, and specific relevant information about the particular service you no longer wish to receive.

Please be aware that when you opt out of receiving communications, it may affect the services you have chosen to receive from us where accepting the communications is a condition of receiving such services. By registering as a user or purchasing products, you consent to receiving administration and transaction related communications.

**Hyperlinks, Widgets and Referrals**

Other websites accessible through the Services (through hyperlinks, advertisements or otherwise) have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult their terms and conditions and privacy policies prior to use.

We do not, even periodically, review the privacy policies or terms of use of third parties and we are not responsible or liable for their privacy practices, availability or reliability of the services they may provide, or the accuracy or completeness of their content. Links to or from any third party site, whether provided by us or not, do not imply any endorsement, approval, or verification by us of any content available on or the policies of such third party sites. By providing access to other websites, Administrator is not recommending the purchase or sale of products or services provided via such linked site. Subject to the terms of applicable service or other agreements, we will remove any link from this Website upon request from the owner of the linked site.

When you click on a hyperlink, sponsored link or banner advertisement, a new browser window or frame containing a third party's website may appear in the foreground with the Website remaining in the background. Any time that you have moved to a new window or frame containing a third party’s website, you will no longer be on the Website, and are no longer protected by this Privacy Policy or our Terms and Conditions.

Our Website and data collection devices include "Widgets," which are interactive mini-programs that run on the Site to provide specific functions as part of the Services. Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through a Widget. The provisions of this Privacy Agreement will apply to all Widgets created and provided by Administrator. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. If any third party Widgets are made available through the Services, the third party’s website privacy policy shall apply when you access the Widget. Any "share" feature available as part of the Services will redirect you to a third party website or Widget, wherein the third party website's privacy policy will apply.

**Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive to enable our Services to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Site are visited and by how many people. Notwithstanding anything else herein, we may partner with third party advertisers who may (themselves or through their partners) place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. These cookies enable more customized ads, content or services to be provided to you. To trigger these cookies, we may pass an encrypted or hashed (non-human readable) identifier corresponding to your email address to a Web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to, these cookies. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to http://www.privacychoice.org/choose.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect or distribute personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. As one measure to ensure that we do not gather personally identifiable information from children under 13, we require that all individuals provide a valid credit card number before completing a purchase order. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe that we have collected personally identifiable information contrary to this policy or, in the United States, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), please contact us by e-mail so that we may delete such information. You can learn more about COPPA at the United States Federal Trade Commission website:

<http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html>

**Notice and Choice**

We may ask for your consent to collect, use, or disclose personal information in certain ways, and you may be required to give your consent in order to use our services. We reserve the right to process personal information in the course of providing services through the Services without the knowledge of individuals involved.  If you wish to opt out of our collection or our disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties, you may contact us at  with a request to do so.  The request should include your name, email address, login information, and any specifics that may help us to prevent the collection of personally identifiable information you do not wish to have collected or disclosed.  Please note that if you opt out of our data collection practices, the Services may be less functional for you.

**Transfers**

We will obtain assurances from its affiliates that they will safeguard personal information consistently with this Privacy Policy. If we learn that an affiliate is using or disclosing personal information in a manner contrary to this Privacy Policy, we will take steps to prevent or stop the use or disclosure. Transfers of information permitted under this notice, either to third parties or amongst Administrator, may include the transfer of data from one jurisdiction to another, such as transfers to and from the United States of America, the UK and Australia.

**Security & Enforcement**

We will take reasonable precautions to protect personal information in its possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, and it will conduct compliance audits of its relevant privacy practices to verify adherence to this Privacy Policy. We cannot guarantee, in every circumstance, the security of the personal information you provide through the Services. All incoming encrypted information is routed through our firewall, which serves as a gatekeeper for our system. Only data containing the correct authorization is permitted past the firewall. Attempts to pass the firewall are constantly monitored for suspicious activity.  Administrator will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Privacy Policy.

**Effective Date**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of  as of 03-30-2014. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we change it, we will post the then-current Privacy Policy on to this page. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective as of the day they are posted.

**Contact Us**

It is important for us to know what visitors have to say about our Website. To contact us with your questions or comments please email us at .
